ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ALES Guide Vol. IX, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- ALES Bibliographies 1956-1960 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- ALES Bibliographies 1932-1935 (Box 120, Folder 21)
- ALES Bibliographies 1936-1940 (Box 120, Folder 22)
- ALES Bibliographies II 1936-40, 1936-1940 (Box 120, Folder 23)
- ALES Bibliographies 1941-45, 1941-1945 (Box 120, Folder 24)
- ALES Bibliographies 1946-1950 (Box 120, Folder 25)
- ALES Bibliographies 1951-1955 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- White Collar Workshops Bibliographies 1935-1960 (Box 120, Folder 27)
- Bulletins 1935-1942 (Box 120, Folder 28)
- Bulletins 1942-1948 (Box 120, Folder 29)
- Bulletins 1952-1960 (Box 120, Folder 30)
- White Collar Workshops Conferences, 1943-1945 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- White Collar Workshops Folders, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Resident Schools on the United Nations 1954 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Residents Schools on the United Nations 1955 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Resident Schools on the United Nations 1956 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Residents Schools on the United Nations 1957 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Resident Schools on the United Nations 1958 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Residents Schools on the United Nations 1959 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Residents Schools on the United Nations 1960 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Resident Schools on the United Nations 1961 (Box 121, Folder 10)
- Conference Programs 1960 (Box 121, Folder 11)
- Conference Programs 1962 (Box 121, Folder 12)
- Conference Programs 1956 (Box 121, Folder 13)
- Conference Programs 1956 (Box 121, Folder 14)
- Conference Programs 1957 (Box 121, Folder 15)
- Conference Programs 1958 (Box 121, Folder 16)
- Conference Programs 1959 (Box 121, Folder 17)
- Conference Programs 1937 (Box 121, Folder 18)
- Conference Programs - 1938 (Box 121, Folder 19)
- Conference Programs 1938 (Box 121, Folder 20)
- Conference Programs - 1939 (Box 121, Folder 21)
- Conference Programs - 1940 (Box 121, Folder 22)
- Conference Programs - 1941 (Box 121, Folder 23)
- Conference Programs - 1942 (Box 121, Folder 24)
- Conference Programs - 1943 (Box 121, Folder 25)
- Conference Programs 1944 (Box 121, Folder 26)
- Conference Programs 1945 (Box 121, Folder 27)
- Conference Programs 1946 (Box 121, Folder 28)
- Conference Programs - 1947 (Box 121, Folder 29)
- Conference Programs - 1948 (Box 121, Folder 30)
- Conference Programs - 1949 (Box 121, Folder 31)
- Conference Programs 1950 (Box 121, Folder 32)
- Conference Programs 1951 (Box 121, Folder 33)
- Conference Programs 1952 - Folder 1 (Box 121, Folder 34)
- Conference Program - 1953 (Box 121, Folder 35)
- Conference Programs 2 - 1953 (Box 121, Folder 36)
- Conference Program 1954 (Box 121, Folder 37)
- Conference Program 1955 (Box 121, Folder 38)
- ALES - Leaflets, Etc. 1931-1935 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- ALES - Leaflets, Etc. 1936-1940 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- ALES - Leaflets, Etc. 1941-1945 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- ALES - Leaflets, Inc. 1946-1950 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- ALES - Leaflets, Etc., 1951-1955 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- ALES - Leaflets, Etc. 1956-1960 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- White Collar Workshops Stories about Schools by Students, 1946 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- White Collar Workshops - Publicity, 1946 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Conference Finding - 1939 New England Workers' Education Conf. (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Conference Findings - Labor Learns Through Action 1939 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Conference Findings - 1940 Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Conference Findings - 1940 Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Conference Findings - 1941 Workers Education and the World Crisis (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Conference Findings - 1942 Summary Report of Institute on Recreation for Workers in Wartime (Box 122, Folder 14)
- Conference Findings - 1943 Annual Conf. of Teachers and Leaders in Workers' Education (Box 122, Folder 15)
- Conference Findings - 1944 Education for Labor Action (Box 122, Folder 16)
- Conference Findings - ALES Conf. for Directors of Work. Educ. Report of Wisconsin, etc. 1945 (Box 122, Folder 17)
- Conference Findings - 1949 Northwest Farmers and Workers Educ. Conf. (Box 122, Folder 18)
- Experiment in St. Louis - Around the World in two Days - 1949 (Box 122, Folder 19)
- Conference Findings - 1953 Annual Washington's Birthday Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 20)
- Conference Findings - 1954 Annual Washington's Birthday Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 21)
- Conference Findings: 1955 Annual Washington's Birthday Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 22)
- Conference Findings: 1955 Annual Washington's Birthday Workers Education Conference (Box 122, Folder 23)
- Findings of Seminar - 1957 Guide Lines to Educational Relationships Between Farmers and Workers (Box 122, Folder 24)
- Pictures - 1950 (Box 122, Folder 25)
- ALES School on World Affairs and the United Nations (Box 122, Folder 26)
  5+ Photographs
- WCW '47, 1947 (Box 122, Folder 27)
- WCW 1948 (Box 122, Folder 28)
- Pictures - 1951 (Box 122, Folder 29)
- 1954 - White Collar Workshops - Pictures (Box 122, Folder 30)
- 1957 Photography (Box 122, Folder 31)
- Women's Seminar on International Affairs (Box 122, Folder 32)
- 1956 White Collar Workshops - Pictures (Box 122, Folder 33)
- ALES - Pictures, Misc. (Box 122, Folder 34)
- School for White Collar Workers Lake Forest 1946 (Box 122, Folder 35)
- Washington's Birthday Groups, 1951 (Box 122, Folder 36)
- Reprints - 1926-1930 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Reprints - 1931-1935 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Reprints - 1936-1940 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Reprints - 1941-1945 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Reprints - 1946-1950 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Reprints - 1951-1955 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Reprints 2 - 1951-1955 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Reprints - 1956-1960 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Reprints - 1961 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- White Collar Workshops Reprints, 1935-1940 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- White Collar Workshops 2 Reprints 1935-1940 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- White Collar Workshops Reprints 1941-1945 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- White Collar Workshops - Reprints 1946-1950 (Box 123, Folder 13)
- White Collar Workshops - Reprints 2 - 1946-1950 (Box 123, Folder 14)
- White Collar Workshops - Reprints 1951-1955 (Box 123, Folder 15)
- American Labor Education Service (1940-1949 Binder) (Box 124, Folder 1)
- American Labor Education Services (1950-1959 Binder) (Box 124, Folder 2)
- ALES (1939-1941) (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Affiliated School for Workers, 1933-1934 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- American Labor Education Service - Card File Index (Boxed), 1927-1962 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  Small box
- Adult Education - It's Philosophy and Practice, 1937 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- Concerning Workers' Education, 1934-1935 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- The Economic Background (For Teachers of Workers' Classes) by Arthur W. Calhoun (Box 125, Folder 4)
- ALES: Photographs Boxes, 11, 28, 31, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- Picture - Bryn Mawr Summer School, Barnard Summer School, Wisc. (Box 125, Folder 6)
- ALES Photos Box 3, 1936 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Box 68, 1952-1953 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- CIO Seminar - 1952 - Photographs Storrs, Conn. (Box 125, Folder 9)
- 2B - Estes Park, Colorado - Photographs 1954 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- Esla Park, Colorado 69/33 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- 1954 United Nations School - Pictures 70/16 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- UN School in N.Y.C., 1955 70/30 (Box 125, Folder 13)
- 2B - 1956 School on the United Nations Photographs (Box 125, Folder 14)
- ALES 1957 UN School Photographs (Box 125, Folder 15)
- U.N. School Photographs, 1958 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  8 Photographs
- 72/8 Removed to. 72/26 UN School, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 17)
- 1953 Northwest Conference (Box 125, Folder 18)
- Box 74 (Box 125, Folder 19)
- Women's Conference' Photographs June 5, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 20)
- 1961 Women's Seminar removed from 75/18 + 75/24 (Box 125, Folder 21)
- Box 78, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 22)
- 2B 2nd Communications Seminar - Photographers 1957 (Box 125, Folder 23)
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 126)